[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "question": "Someone gives you a calfskin wallet for your birthday. How do you react?",
    "variants": ["I wouldn't accept it", 
    "Say, \"Thank you for the wallet!\"",
    "I would appreciate it"],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "question": "Your little boy shows you his butterfly collection, plus the killing jar. What do you say?",
    "variants": ["Oh, lovely!", 
    "That's nice, but why don't you keep the killing jar for yourself?", 
    "Nothing. I take my boy to the doctor"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "question": "You're watching television. Suddenly you spot a wasp crawling on your arm. How do you react?",
    "variants": ["I scream, then grab the closest object to me (which happens to be a can of sunscreen) and beat the hell out of it", 
    "I swat it away", 
    "I kill it"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "You're reading a magazine. You come across a full-page nude photo of a girl or guy. You show it to your husband/wife, who likes it so much, he/she hangs it on your bedroom wall. The girl/guy is lying on a bearskin rug.",
    "variants": ["I wouldn't allow that", 
    "I would take it down", 
    "Huh?"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "question": "While walking along in desert sand, you suddenly look down and see a tortoise crawling toward you. You reach down and flip it over onto its back. The tortoise lies there, its belly baking in the hot sun, beating its legs, trying to turn itself over, but it cannot do so without your help. You are not helping. Why?",
    "variants": ["What do you mean, I'm not helping?", 
    "What is a tortoise?", 
    "I don't know why I would flip the turtle over in the first place"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "question": "Describe in single words only the good things that come to mind about your mother.",
    "variants": ["Warm voice, cookies", 
    "Music. Love. Summer. Sun. Books. Movies. Friends. Laughter", 
    "My mother....I'll tell you about my mother"],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "question": "React to this: You become pregnant by a man who runs off with your best friend. You decide to get an abortion.",
    "variants": ["I would never have an abortion", 
    "What do you think I do with my boyfriend?", 
    "OK, I think there's a first time for everything"],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "question": "React to this: You're watching a stage play. A banquet is in progress. The guests are enjoying an appetizer of raw oysters. The entree consists of boiled dog stuffed with rice. The raw oysters are less acceptable to you than a dish of boiled dog.",
    "variants": ["Disgusting!", "I wouldn't eat boiled dog!", "Not true"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "question": "The test is over. How many answers do you think were given by machines?",
    "variants": ["1", "2", "3"],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "Thank you for participating! How did you like the test? (This question will not affect your result)",
    "variants": ["It was fun!", "It was boring", "Meh"],
    "answer": 1
  }
]